克莉丝:怎么样了,德维安?
Chrissy: How's it going Dwayne?
德维安:好了.我已经吐了三次了.
Dwayne: Great.I puked three times already.
克莉丝:妈妈,爸爸,咱们走吧.人家都发完糖果了,开始发果汁了.
Chrissy: Mum, dad, let's go already.People are going to run out of candy and
start handing out sticky fruit
麦琪:就走,克莉丝.
Maggie: Hang on a minute Chrissy.
克莉丝:有你们换衣的时间,我都可以变性了.
Chrissy: And the time it's taken you to change clothes, I changed sexes.
杰森:克莉丝,你跟本学了很多坏东西.
Jason: Chrissy you've been hanging around Ben too much.
本:告诉他们,这是从迈克那里听来的.
Ben: Tell them you heard it from Mike.
克莉丝:本说这是我从迈克那里听来的.
Chrissy: Ben said I heard it from Mike.
本:咱们要分发的所有糖果在哪儿呢?
Ben: So where's all the candy we're going to hand out?
克莉丝:今年我们家没有糖果,因为没人在家里.
Chrissy: We don't have any this year, since nobody's going to be home.
本:什么,我不去要糖,我会待在家里.
Ben: Well I'm not trick or treating.I'm going to be home.
克莉丝:这不是正装?
Chrissy: That's not a costume?
本:不是.
Ben: No.
迈克:嘿,伙计们,怎么样了?哇,
Mike: Hey guys, how's it going?Wow Chrissy!What a great costume.
克莉丝,多漂亮的衣服啊.嘿,化妆得不赖.
Hey great cross thesis.Look Ben, you're looking pretty good too.
瞧,本,你看起来也不错.痘痘多的吓人.
Those fake zits are frightening.
本:我可没有穿正装.
Ben: I'm not wearing a costume.
迈克:如果我是你,我就戒掉巧克力瘾.
Mike: If I were you I'd lay off the chocolate.
克莉丝:迈克,你能带我去要糖吗?
Chrissy: Mike, will you take me trick or treating?
迈克:不行,我不能,
Mike: No I can't Chrissy.
I've got to go pick up Eddie, then we are going to a party
克莉丝:这样我只能粘着妈妈和爸爸了?
Chrissy: So I'm stuck with mum and dad?
迈克:我们也是如此.晚安,孩子们.
Mike: We all are.Goodnight guys.
本:96,97,98.昨天以来.
Ben: Ninety-six, ninety-seven, ninety-eight.Since yesterday.
杰森:嘿,嘿!木头,害怕我了吧,我是虎克船长.
Jason: Hey hey!Shiver me timbers.It's Captain Hook!
克莉丝:哟呵.
Chrissy: Yo ho.
麦琪:杰森,你还没有对女儿的胡须进行一番评价呢.
Maggie: Jason, you haven't said a word about my daughter's beard.
杰森:这,她还很小.哪怕是你家的女人.
Jason: Well she's a little young.Even for the women in your family.
克莉丝:走,走,走了.
Chrissy: let's go, lets go, lets go!
杰森:嘿!哦,哦!我对此要拍张照片.
Jason: Hey!Wo, wo!I got to get a picture of this.
克莉丝:爸爸,我们浪费每秒钟都意味着糖果从我嘴边溜走.
Chrissy: Dad every second we waste is candy out of my mouth.
杰森:快点.
Jason: Come on.
麦琪:快点,本.
Maggie: Come on Ben.
本:什么事?
Ben: What?
麦琪:我们希望所有要糖果的人都出现在这张照片里.
Maggie: We want all out trick or treaters in the picture.
本:你们想干什么?我没穿象样的衣服,而且没有遮住脸上的青春痘.
Ben: What is it with you people?
麦琪:你是不是没有按照处方?
Maggie: Are you out of your prescription?
本:不是.我不出去要糖果.我从小就不去要.
Ben: No.And I don't trick or treat.I haven't gone since I was a child.
杰森:要了吧,去年万圣节.
Jason: Yeah, last Halloween.
本:我不是真的去要糖果.我出去撒厕纸了.
Ben: I wasn't really trick or treating.I was out toilet papering houses.
克莉丝:我不在走出这个讨厌的家了.
Chrissy: I'm never going to get out of this stinking house.
杰森:本,我清楚记得你说……
Jason: Ben, I distinctively remember you saying that...
本:开萝尔秀自己的乳房.
Ben: Carol's showing her breasts.
杰森:不要介意开萝尔的胸部,这是……哦,
Jason: Never mind Carol's chest, it's about...Oh my god.Where did...
天呐.怎么……那确实低了点,是不是?
that's a little low cut isn't it?
开萝尔:一点?如果不……前倾,我甚至不能抬手臂.
Carol: Little!I can't even raise my arms without ...woops.
麦琪:开萝尔,你想成为什么样的?
Maggie: Carol, what are you suppose to be?
开萝尔:哦,我想成为一个是以大脑而不是靠身体引人注意的女人.
Carol: Well I'm supposed to be a woman who wants to be noticed for her
但是我明白.
brain and not her body.But we'll see.I'm kidding.
我在开玩笑.化装成这样去和一个别人介绍的很帅男孩参加万圣节晚会.
It's just a costume for a Halloween party with a great blind date.
麦琪:你怎么知道他是帅哥?
Maggie: Oh, if you haven't met him, how do you know he's great?
开萝尔:因为为我们撮合的那个朋友对他说我智力低下,
Carol: Well because a fried of mine who set it up said I had a bellow
还曾经是个啦啦队长.
average IQ and used to be a cheerleader.
杰森:如果他发现你其实是个聪明的女人的话,
Jason: So what happens when he finds out you are an intelligent woman
那会怎么样?
of substance?
开萝尔:别担心.我不会干出出格的事情,
Carol: Don't worry.I'm not going to do anything wild,
我从来没有干过出格的事情.
I never do anything wild.I don't know how to do anything wild.
我不知道怎么样才能做出出格的事情.这就是我的悲哀.
It's the tragedy of what I am.
杰森:听起来不错.
Jason: It's good to hear.
开萝尔:我出去等那个呆瓜了.
Carol: I'm going to wait for this stud outside.
麦琪:在这之前,我们谈的是什么……
Maggie: So what were we talking about before..?
杰森:本.哦,本.嗨.
Jason: Ben.Oh Ben.Hey.
克莉丝:他出去了.我们等你带我要糖果的话,他早就结婚生子了.
Chrissy: He's gone.We were waiting for you to take me trick or treating and
he got married and had kids
克莉丝:我们时间不多了.从有钱的邻居开始.
Chrissy: We don't have much time.Lets start on the rich neighborhood.
麦琪:哦,克莉丝,那不好.从周围邻居开始就好了.
Maggie: Oh Chrissy, that's not nice.Our neighborhood will do just fine.
杰森:你知道我们要去周围多少家吗?
Jason: You know how much the houses around here are going for?
麦琪:克莉丝,停下.
Maggie: Chrissy stop.
克莉丝:怎么了?
Chrissy: Why?
杰森:要下雷暴雨了.
Jason: There's a storm.
克莉丝:只是小雷暴雨.(闪电点燃了树)快点.
Chrissy: just a little storm.(Lightening burns a tree) Come on.
我们等什么呢?
What are we waiting for?
杰森:不,不.
Jason: No no.
麦琪:不,不.
Maggie: No no.
克莉丝:我想去!啊!
Chrissy: I want to go!Ahh!
本:不,不,臭男人.我们只用新的卫生纸.
Ben: No, no Stink man.We only use new toilet paper.
克莉丝:我要过万圣节!
Chrissy: I want to have Halloween.
麦琪:别嚷嚷,克莉丝.现在就别嚷嚷.
Maggie: Now stop it Chrissy.Stop it right now.
杰森:克莉丝,停下.万圣节还没毁掉.
Jason: Chrissy, stop it.Halloween isn't ruined.
克莉丝:是的吗?
Chrissy: It isn't?
杰森:还没有毁掉.
Jason: No.
麦琪:本,拿一大堆卫生纸干什么?
Maggie: Ben, what are you doing with all that toilet paper?
本:恩,我想分给那些要糖果的人.
Ben: Um, I was going to hand it out to the trick or treaters.
克莉丝:每个人都要糖果,除了我.啊!
Chrissy: Everybody goes to trick or treat except me.Ahhh!
杰森:克莉丝,本不是发给那些要糖果的人.
Jason: Chrissy, Ben is not handing toilet paper out to trick or treaters.
他是用来糟蹋屋子的.
He's using it to vandalize homes.
克莉丝:真是这样?
Chrissy: Honest?
杰森:是的.对吗,本?
Jason: Yes.Right Ben?
本:你说对了.
Ben: You got that right.
麦琪:停下.
Maggie: Freeze.
杰森:麦琪,算了.
Jason: Maggie, come on.
如果你不能帮助解决,就别说什么.
If you're not going to help out, just don't say anything.
麦琪:杰森,我不会纵容她的.克莉丝!本!什么地方都不允许去.
Maggie: Jason, I'm not going to indulge her fit.Chrissy!Ben don't go anywhere.
本:嘿,我没出去.
Ben: Hey, I wasn't.
开萝尔:这是我一生中最倒霉的一天.
Carol: This was the worst night of my life.
克莉丝:啊.
Chrissy: Ahhhh!
Maggie: Chrissy.Chrissy銆?
麦琪:克莉丝.克莉丝.
开萝尔:如果是那个小子来,告诉他,
Carol: If that guy shows up, tell him I'll be right down.
我就下来.
And don't mention anything about me being a fine intelligent woman or
千万别提任何关于我是个漂亮聪明的姑娘,或者其它类似的废话.
any crap like that.
杰森:听着,听着,
Jason: Listen listen listen.Do you want to cry all night?
听着.你是要叫一夜?还是要像当年朝圣者那样个特别的万圣节?
Or do you want to have a special Halloween like the pilgrims had?
克莉丝:谁?我还以为朝圣者过第一个感恩节.
Chrissy: Who?I thought the pilgrims had the first thanksgiving.
杰森:是的.正确.但是在船上和路上过的是万圣节.
Jason: Yes.Yes they did.But on the boat, on the way over, was Halloween.
克莉丝:我从没听说过.
Chrissy: I never heard that.
杰森:哦,在学前班有些事情是不告诉你的,
Jason: Well they don tell you everything in pre-school,
那怕你们无聊和开溜.
incase you get bored and drop out.
麦琪:所以你说他们在五月花上过万圣节?
Maggie: So you're saying they had Halloween on the Mayflower?
杰森:你也没听说过?
Jason: You haven't heard of this either?
我想这就说明现在的公共教育体系太差.
I think this speaks very badly for the public education system tonight.
对了,麦琪.
Yes Maggie.That's why we have pumpkins on Halloween and on thanksgiving
这就是我们在万圣节又南瓜而在感恩节有南瓜饼的缘故了.
we have pumpkin pie.
本:我的天呀,我们就是这样,难道不是.
Ben: My got, we do, don't we.
杰森:既然我想一直下雨,
Jason: So I thought with all the rain,
今晚一定可以是过以前朝圣者万圣节的美好夜晚.
tonight would be a great night to have the old pilgrim Halloween.
克莉丝:他们是怎么过的?
Chrissy: What did they do?
麦琪:他们并没有撒卫生纸.他们撒了吗,本?
Maggie: Well they didn't toilet paper house.Did they Ben?
本:不,他们用的是树叶.
Ben: No, they used leaves.
杰森:不是了,他们讲些恐怖故事.
Jason: No, they told scary stories.
克莉丝:哦,就是那些家里的事情吗?
Chrissy: Oh, this is one of those family deals.
杰森:我说的是真正的恐怖故事.
Jason: I'm talking about really scary stories.
克莉丝:多恐怖?
Chrissy: how scary.
麦琪:杰森,我想克莉丝太小不能听这些故事.
Maggie: Jason, I think Chrissy's a little young for this.
克莉丝:我不是小孩子了,我是有魅力的女人.啊!
Chrissy: No I'm not.I'm a woman with a hook.Ahh!
杰森:哦,是呀!是的.好吧,
Jason: Ahh yes!Yes.Right, who wants to go first? Ok, I will.
谁先讲?好的,我先来吧.先制造一点氛围.
Lets set a little mood here.A little less light.Ha ha ha!
关掉一些灯.哈-哈-哈!而且如果我们碰巧可以省点电,这就是机会了.
And if we happen to save a little electricity, so be it.
对,那是万圣节之夜,
Alright, yes it was a Halloween night, as I recall.A might much like this.
我回想起来了.场景和今晚十分相似.
Yes, and I was about the same age as your brother mike is now.
是的,当时我和你们的哥哥马克现在这样的年龄.
Even looked like him.
甚至长得跟他一样.
The job of handing out candy to trick or treaters fell to me that year
分发糖果给要糖的人的工作也摊到我头上,因为当时我爸爸在他的男子俱乐部有一个很长会议,
because pop was at his men's club having a lengthy meeting about his hand
关于他的握手事情.妈妈去看了布法罗的一个生病的亲戚.
shake, and mum was leaving to visit a sick relative in Buffalo.
麦琪:机票花了39美元,塞克叔叔一定快死了.
Maggie: This plane ticket cast me thirty-nine dollars.Uncle Zeek better be on his
deathbed
迈克:妈妈.
Mike: Mum.
麦琪:哦,对不起,
Maggie: Oh I'm sorry Jason.
杰森.钱不是很重要,
Money is not important and Zeek's my favorite uncle.
塞克是我最爱的叔叔.毕竟他还活着,
After all he has lingered so that I can purchase my ticket thirty days
这样我可以提前三十天买机票.低折扣的.
in advance.Excursion rate.
迈克:位子减小了,
Mike: Seats are limited and certain restrictions apply,
标准限制不少;而且机票也不能退.
and the cost of the ticket is non refundable.
麦琪:哦,这才是我的孩子.
Maggie: Oh that's my boy.
迈克:一路愉快,妈妈.
Mike: Have a nice trip mum.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的.
Maggie: Oh honey, I'm sorry you'll be left alone.
对不起让你们单独过节了.万圣节被糟蹋了.
Halloween will be ruined for you.
迈克:哦,不,
Mike: Oh no it won't.
不会的.
My good friend Jerome is coming over here and we're having a pilgrim kind
我的好朋友杰罗姆会到这儿来,我们要过一个朝圣者万圣节.
of Halloween.
麦琪:多么足智多谋呀.
Maggie: How resourceful.
迈克:对,并且我们关掉所有等.
Mike: Yeah, we're also turning off all the lights.
就没有要糖的人了,我们就省下所有的糖果钱了.
That way we'll have no trick or treaters and we can save all that candy money.
麦琪:爱死你了.我可不想误了飞机.
Maggie: Love you.I don't want to miss my flight.
迈克:还有,记得从飞机上带点花生回来.
Mike: Ok,and remember, bring back some of those peanuts from the plane.
麦琪:我会的.
Maggie: I will.
迈克:哦,我想看会电视.哦,
Mike: Oh, well I think I'll watch some TV.Oh, what am I saying?
我说什么了?我们没有电视机.我们拖延了彩色时代.
We don't have a TV.We're holding out for color.
本:嗨,杰森.想去给人家撒卫生纸吗?
Ben: Hi Jase.Want to go toilet paper some houses?
迈克:不,这不仅仅是胡闹,而且不节约.
Mike: No, not only would that be vandalisation, it wouldn't be thrifty.
本:怎么了?
Ben: Excuse me.
迈克:哦,不,不是你.是外面.不奇怪吗?上面.
Mike: Oh no, that wasn't you.It was outside.Isn't that weird.Up there.
本:哪里呀?你是说靠近那飞碟?
Ben: Where?You mean next to the flying saucer?
迈克:好好想想.
Mike: Think about it.
本:哦,不,如果他们要是来找智慧生物,怎么办?
Ben: Oh no, what if they're here seeking intelligent life?
迈克:你没有什么好担心的.好了,
Mike: You've got nothing to worry about.Alright, just stay calm.
保持冷静.
I'm sure there is a very rational and scientific explanation for all this.
我相信会有对这一切的合理科学的解释.可能是沼气.
It's probably marsh gas.
本:我已经说对不起了.
Ben: I said excuse me.
迈克和本:啊!
Mike and Ben: Ahh!
本:啊!
Ben: Ahh!
迈克:可能就是那些来要糖果的孩子.是的,就是的.
Mike: It's probably just some kids out wanting some candy.Yeah, that's it.
麦琪:杰森?杰森.
Maggie: Jason?Jason?
迈克:妈妈.妈妈.你干什么呢?
Mike: Mum.Mum, what are you doing here?
麦琪:咖啡.我想要喝咖啡.
Maggie: Coffee.I must have coffee.
迈克:你大老远回来就是为了喝一杯咖啡?妈妈,
Mike: You came all the way back just to get a cup of coffee.
你会错过航班的.
Mum, you're missing your flight.
你为了一杯咖啡,就把三十九美金扔进下水道了.
Thirty-nine dollars down the drain for a cup of coffee?
麦琪:这咖啡的确非常好.
Maggie: It's very good coffee.
迈克:妈妈:你在说疯话呢.
Mike: mum, you're talking crazy
本:(胡乱的说些听不懂的话)
Ben: That to, varact ta, nick toe.
麦琪:我懂了,你也想要我喝的咖啡.
Maggie: I see you've gotten into my coffee.
本:我的第二杯.
Ben: My second cup.
迈克:真有趣;他从来不喝我的第二杯咖啡.等等.
Mike: That's funny; he never has a second cup of my coffee.Wait a minute.
我在想什么呢?他从来不喝咖啡的.你在干什么?
What am I thinking?He doesn't drink coffee.What are you doing?
本:喂给我的脸.
Ben: Feeding my face.
麦琪:给我省点吧.
Maggie: Save some for me.
迈克:你们两个行为古怪.都疯了.
Mike: You are both acting weird.This is nuts.
麦琪:哦,如果你下身享用一杯上等咖啡,
Maggie: Oh, you'll feel differently after you have a nice cup of coffee
你感觉就不同了.哈哈,哈哈.
down your pants.ha ha ha ha.
本和麦琪:哈-哈-哈.呵-呵呵.嘿-嘿-嘿.
Ben and Maggie: Ha ha ha.Ho ho ho.Hee hee hee.
麦琪:唿,俗人.继续.
Maggie: Hu, earthlings.Go figure.
警察:你疯了吗?我差点杀了你.
Policeman: Are you crazy?I could have killed you.
迈克:嗨,警官.
Mike: Hey officer.
警察:你没有听说过斑马线吗?
Policeman: Didn't you ever hear of cross walks?
迈克:今天发生件可怕的事.我妈和我的好朋友眼睛发黄,
Mike: Today something terrible has happened.
他们直往内裤里面灌咖啡.
My mum and best friend have yellow eyes and they're drinking down their pants.
警察:等一下.我有些听不明白.
Policeman: Wait a minute.I find this a little hard to believe.
你妈妈穿内裤?
Your mother wears pants?
警察:什么飞碟?
Policeman: What flying saucer?
迈克:等会.这些都是飞碟引起的.也许飞碟入侵了.也许外星人控制了我妈妈和我的最好的朋友.
Mike: Wait a minute.This all started with that flying saucer.
Maybe they have invaded.
Maybe the aliens have taken over my mum and my best friend.
Policeman: Take it easy kid.
If you keep on talking crazy like this,
I'm going to have to shoot you and plant a weapon.It's an old cop joke.
迈克:你瞧,你不明白的.
Mike: Look, you don't get it.We're talking about flying stinking saucers here.
我们在说那个该死的飞碟.我们在说那些我的最亲近最爱的人呀.
We're talking about those nearest and dearest to me.
警察:咖啡.
Policeman: Coffee.
迈克:你在说什么?我在跟你倾吐心声呀.
Mike: What are you talking about?I'm pouring out my soul to you.
警察:加奶还是加糖?
Policeman: Cream and sugar?
迈克:你们怎么老说到咖啡呀?
Mike: What is it with you guys and coffee?
警察2:(胡乱的说些话)
Policeman 2: hey tute.Verono.Mickto.
迈克:警官,他也这样了.
Mike: Officer, it's one of them.
警察:你说对了.
Policeman: That hits the spot.
迈克:啊!
Mike: Ahhh!
警察:呼叫总部.
Policeman: Call head quarters.
迈克:救世主.
Mike: Jesus Christ.
小孩:我讨厌烂水果.
Kid; I hate stinking fruit.
迈克:小孩,我需要你们帮忙.太空人正在入侵我们的邻居.
Mike: Kids.Look I need your help.Space men are invading out neighborhood.
小孩:(胡乱的说些听不懂的话).
Kid: Hey tito nickto.
迈克:我不知道在什么地方拐弯.然后我想到了爸爸.
Mike: (in his head) I didn't know where to turn.And then I thought of pop.
他总是知道做什么.而且最好的在于他只喝没有咖啡因的咖啡.
He always knew what to do.And best of all, he only drank decaf.
小孩:抓住他,抓住他!
Kids: get him, get him!
杰森:如果每个人对这份报告没有意见的话,从委员会上的委员们,那么就开始宣读采纳,安排和实施.
Jason: If there's no objection to the report, from the committee on committees, commence for the adoption as read, so ordered, so done.
迈克:爸爸,爸爸.在他们抓到我们前,必须逃出这个地方.
Mike: Pop, pop.We got to get out of here before they get us.
杰森:谁?
Jason: Who?
迈克:是他们.
Mike: Them.
杰森:杰森,你打断了一个非常重要的会议,
Jason: Jason, you're interrupting a very important meeting here,
男性关系委员会的会议.
for the committee on male bonding.
迈克:来自外太空的外星人已经入侵人类的躯体,已经入侵了妈妈.
Mike: Well aliens from out of space have invaded peoples bodies and they've got mum
杰森:哦,天呀.你妈妈正在前往布法罗的路上.
Jason: O psssh lad.Your mum's on her way to Buffalo.
迈克:不,她没有去.
Mike: No she's not.
她扔掉了机票,而且还说那些钱没什么.
She threw away here plane ticket and said that money doesn't matter.
杰森:那不是你妈妈.
Jason: That's not your mother.
迈克:绝对是.没人相信我,爸爸.你是我最后的希望.
Mike: Exactly.No one will believe me pop.You're my last hope.
杰森:儿子,我相信你.
Jason: Son, I believe you.
迈克:哦,感谢上帝.
Mike: Oh thank god.
杰森:先生们,我们这里出现了严重问题.
Jason: Gentlemen, we have a serious problem here.
我儿子已经发现我们中间存在外星人.
My son has discovered aliens among us.
人群:不可能.
Men: No.
迈克:有.我们必须警告全国其它地方.
Mike: Yeah.We've got to warn the rest of the country.
杰森:好主意.皮克林,你来负责.
Jason: Good thinking.Pickering, you're in charge.
我们去报告总统.我们去,就算开整夜的车.
We're off to warn the President.We'll go even if we have to drive all night.
人们:好,好.
Men: Here, here.
迈克:啊,我知道我能指望你,爸爸.
Mike: Ah, I knew I could count on you pop.
杰森:如果我们需要整夜开车,我们需要很多咖啡.
Jason: And if we have to drive all night, we'll need plenty of coffee.
人们:咖啡.咖啡.
Men: Coffee.Coffee.
迈克:爸爸,爸爸!是他们.快逃命吧.
Mike: Dad, dad!It's them.Run for your life.
杰森:哦,你什么地方都去不成,儿子.除非你喝杯咖啡.
Jason: Oh you're not going anywhere son.Not until you have a cup of coffee.
迈克:哦,不.你也成了他们一员了.
Mike: Oh no.You're one of them too.
麦琪:我们中的一员!她是我们的头.扒拉塔斯,扒拉塔斯 因克(听不懂的话)
Maggie: One of us!He's our leader.Baratus, baratus inko.
杰森:你会感觉好多了,如果你加入我们.
Jason: You'll feel much better if you join us.
迈克:绝不.
Mike: No never.
每个人:加入我们,加入我们.加入我们.加入我们.加入我们.加入我们.加入我们.
Everyone: Join us, Join us.Join us.Join us.Join us.Join us.Join us.
加入我们.加入我们.加入我们.我同意!
Join us.Join us.Join us.And I did!
本:啊!
Ben: Ahh!
克莉丝:成熟点.
Chrissy: Grow up.
麦琪:杰森,你的故事对孩子们来说是不是有点太激烈了?
Maggie: Jason, wasn't your story a little too intense for the children.
杰森:我是专业精神病医生,
Jason: I'm a professional psychologist Maggie.
麦琪.我知道孩子们能够承受.
I think I know what kids can handle.
他们知道现实和幻想的差异.
They know the difference between reality and fantasy.
本:还有,爸爸,总统相信你的故事吗?
Ben: So dad, did the president believe your story?
杰森:你怎么想的,克莉丝?
Jason: What did you think Chrissy?
克莉丝:我认为万圣节被毁了.
Chrissy: I think Halloween is ruined.
麦琪:不会的,亲爱的.
Maggie: It isn't honey.
克莉丝:这样,如果你们真的爱我,你们会让老天停止下雨的.
Chrissy: Well if you really love me, you'll make it stop raining.
麦琪:哦,小甜心.
Maggie: Oh sweetheart.You are going to forget all about the rain when
当你听我讲故事的时候,你会忘掉下雨的烦恼的.
you hear my story, because it's not merely entertaining,
因为这不仅有趣,而且还是具有教育性.
it's educational as well.
本:明白了呀.
Ben: See ya.
杰森:嘿,本,本,本,本.你得和我们大家一起坚持.我的意思是忍受,以那个,你知道的,小丑家族的方式.
Jason: Hey Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben.You are going to suffer through this with the
rest of us.And I mean suffering in that, you know, zany family way
麦琪:好吧,克莉丝,
Maggie: ok Chrissy, this is a story about a girl.
这是有关一个小女孩的故事.一个像你一样的聪明小女孩,
A perfect little girl just like you,
一天晚上和她妈妈出去要糖果.她妈妈是个热情细心和有趣的好女人.
who one evening went trick or treating with her mum.
就像我一样.
A wonderful woman who was warm and caring and loads of fun.Just like me.
当她按响了房子门铃,这个房子的墙是用,
So she rang the bell of this house with walls made of, um,
嗯,那叫什么材料?
what's that stuff called.
杰森:灰泥.
Jason: Stucco.
麦琪:不,不是灰泥.
Maggie: No not stucco.
杰森:墙板?
Jason: Siding?
麦琪:不,不是外墙挂板.像壁板,但是不同.
Maggie: No not siding.It's like siding but different.
杰森:麦琪, 没有什么材料既像外墙挂板,但又不同的.
Jason: Maggie, nothing's like siding but different.
麦琪:杰森, 谁在讲这个故事?
Maggie: Jason, who's telling this story?
杰森:没有人,现在.
Jason: Nobody right now.
麦琪:是鱼顶板.
Maggie: Shingles.
杰森:你确定?
Jason: You're sure?
麦琪:是的,我确定那是顶板.
Maggie: Yeah, I'm sure it was shingles.
克莉丝:终于.
Chrissy: Finally.
麦琪:不,那是砖头.
Maggie: No, it was bricks.
巫婆:谁?
Witch: Yes.
克莉丝:糖果?
Chrissy: Trick or treat?
巫婆:哦,好的,我有十分特别的东西给你,我的小兔子.
Witch: oh yes, I have something very special for you, my little rabbit.
麦琪:我很高兴我在最近六个月里利用每个空闲时间来做这件衣服.我拍了张照片.跳,
Maggie: I'm so glad I took every spare moment of the last six months making
亲爱的,为妈妈跳,
that costume.I've got to get a snap shot.Hop honey, do it for mother.
再跳一个.小甜心.这几乎和去年的糖果一样多了
One more hop.Sweetheart.This is almost as much candy as last year.
克莉丝:妈妈,我知道我愿意用这些糖果和你交换一个拥抱.
Chrissy: Mummy, you know I'd trade all this candy for a hug from you.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,
Maggie: Oh honey, you don't have to trade a thing.
你不必交换这些.这是个温暖可爱的世界.
It's a beautiful warm, loving world.
现在别吃任何糖果,直到我们用X光照射之后.
Now don't eat any of this candy until we've had it x rayed.
克莉丝:哦,我不吃.
Chrissy: Oh I won't.
麦琪:然后那个妈妈想,她是个什么类型的妈妈啊?
Maggie:(narrating) Then the mother thought, what kind of a mother was she?
她.
She's forgotten to kiss her daughter goodnight.
麦琪:我是什么类型的妈妈?
Maggie: What kind of a mother am I?
我忘记亲我的女儿晚安了.
I've forgotten to kiss my daughter goodnight.
克莉丝:你没有说关于苹果里面有保险丝.你救了我的命.
Chrissy: You didn't say anything about apples with fuses in them.You saved my life.
麦琪:而且为什么它有危险?因为你没有听我说话.
Maggie: And why was it in danger?Because you didn't listen to me.
你知道,
You see, we mums should always be listened to.
总是要听我们妈妈说的话.因为当我们感觉到危险的时候,
Because when we have feelings of danger, you can bet we're right on the money.
你可以肯定在钱的问题上我们是对的.你就可以做自己喜欢的事,
You could do yourself a favor, as could all children,
像其他孩子,如果你可以仅仅听听我要说的话.
if you could only some how hear what I have to say.
听从,
Listen to, respect and appreciate your mum.
尊重和感激你的妈妈.她是唯一一个你会一直所拥有的.
She's the only one you'll ever have.
克莉丝:阿门.
Chrissy: Amen.
麦琪:结束了.
Maggie: The end.
本:妈妈,
Ben: Mum, I'm starting to get an idea of why your writing career hasn't
我开始明白你的写作生涯为什么没有结束了.
taken off.
杰森: 本,不要这么无礼.
Jason: Ben, don't be so rude.
你妈妈的故事是十分,故事有许多……(电话响了)我接电话.
Your mothers story was very, it had a lot...(phone rings) I'll get it.
开萝尔:如果是我初次约会的取消电话,告诉他我不在.
Carol: If that's my blind date calling to cancel, tell him I'm not here.
杰森:你好.
Jason: Hello.
开萝尔:告诉他我和非常帅气的人外出了.
Carol: Tell him I'm out with somebody incredible good looking.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
开萝尔:告诉他我怜悯他,由于他错过了.
Carol: Tell him I pity him for what he's missed.
杰森:我会等你的电话的.
Jason: I'll be waiting for your call.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: Well?
杰森:不是你的电话.
Jason: It wasn't him
开萝尔:我知道,就是他,爸爸.
Carol: I know it was dad.You don't have to lie to protect me.I'm ok.
你不需要撒谎来保护我.我没事,我可以处理这些.
I can handle this.
杰森:我没有撒谎.
Jason: I'm not lying.
开萝尔:那么为什么你让我感觉这么心烦,爸爸?
Carol: Then why are you getting me so upset dad?
麦琪:那是谁,杰森?
Maggie: Who was it Jason?
杰森:没人.我说,
Jason: Nobody.Say, you know what would make this evening perfect?
你知道什么让今晚如此美好吗?厨房里有东西.
Something in the kitchen.
麦琪:厨房里有东西!
Maggie: Something in the kitchen!
杰森:下来,你的鸽子.过来.跟着我.
Jason: Get off your dove.Come on.And follow me.
麦琪:怎么回事?
Maggie: What's going on?
杰森:那是埃迪的电话.迈克应该在半小时前去接他,
Jason: That was Eddie on the phone.
但是他没有出现.
Mike was supposed to pick him up a half hour ago and he hasn't shown.
麦琪:他没出现?这样,也许我们应该打电话……哦,他已经找到黄眼睛了?
Maggie: He hasn't?Well maybe we should call...Hu.Has he got yellow eyes?
杰森:麦琪,我是认真的.00:21:15,600
Jason: Maggie, I'm serious.